hitlink.com 2016-10-29

# Welcome to HitLink

**THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT DISCLOSES THE PRIVACY PRACTICES FOR HitLink.com**

**Information Collection and Use of Information:**

In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give his contact information (email address). This information is used to contact the user about the service and products we provide or wish to provide. We will not sell, share, or rent personal information to others.

**Security:**

This website takes every precaution to protect our users personal information. When a user submits sensitive information via our site, the information is protected both online and off-line. Only the qualified staff of this site can access personal information of the users. 

**Correction/Updating Personal Information:**

If a user's personally identifiable information changes, we provide a way to correct that user's personal data provided to us. This can be done within the member area.

**Right to Cancel:  
**  
Our users can cancel membership and be removed from all newsletters and databases. To do this a link is provided at the end of system generated email messages from HitLink.com, click the link and you will be taken to a web page where you will have to verify your self with your email and password. You will then be removed from our newsletters and database.

**Site and Service Updates:  
**  
We may send the user site and service announcement updates. We communicate with the users to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their accounts via email.

**Notification of Changes:  
**  
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy we will notify our members by way of an email. The members can then decide if they wish to continue their membership based on the new policy or remove their accounts.
